{"Items":[{"puzzleId":1,"question":"What kind of dog doesn't bite or bark?","answer":"Hot dog","confusion_1":"Gentle dog","confusion_2":"Old dog\r"},{"puzzleId":2,"question":"What is the smallest room in the world?","answer":"Mushroom","confusion_1":"Your bedroom","confusion_2":"A room in Shanghai\r"},{"puzzleId":3,"question":"What kind of water should people drink in order to be healthy?","answer":"Well water","confusion_1":"Clean water","confusion_2":"Mineral water\r"},{"puzzleId":4,"question":"What will you break once you say it?","answer":"Silence","confusion_1":"Promise","confusion_2":"Love\r"},{"puzzleId":5,"question":"Will liars be honest after they die?","answer":"They lie still","confusion_1":"No, they won't change","confusion_2":"Yes, they cannot lie\r"},{"puzzleId":6,"question":"What always goes up and never goes down?","answer":"Your age","confusion_1":"Your height","confusion_2":"Your weight\r"},{"puzzleId":7,"question":"Why did the boy make his dog sit in the sun?","answer":"He wants a hot dog","confusion_1":"The dog loves sun","confusion_2":"To warm the dog\r"},{"puzzleId":8,"question":"Why is the library the highest building?","answer":"It has the most stories.","confusion_1":"The library is great","confusion_2":"Knowledge is priceless.\r"},{"puzzleId":9,"question":"What bird lifts heavy things?","answer":"A crane","confusion_1":"An eagle","confusion_2":"A swallow\r"},{"puzzleId":10,"question":"What's the poorest bank in the world?","answer":"River bank","confusion_1":"A bank has no money","confusion_2":"Bank during the war\r"},{"puzzleId":11,"question":"What stays hot even if put it in a fridge?","answer":"Pepper","confusion_1":"Something on fire","confusion_2":"Everything in summer\r"},{"puzzleId":12,"question":"With which hand do you write?","answer":"Neither, the pen","confusion_1":"The right hand","confusion_2":"The left hand\r"},{"puzzleId":13,"question":"A mouse has a large pocket. What is it ?","answer":"A kangaroo","confusion_1":"A bat","confusion_2":"A mouse in pocket\r"},{"puzzleId":14,"question":"What do you know about the kings of France?","answer":"They are all dead","confusion_1":"Napoleon","confusion_2":"There are 30 kings\r"},{"puzzleId":15,"question":"What must you do before you return a book?","answer":"Borrow a book","confusion_1":"Take a selfie","confusion_2":"Read the book\r"},{"puzzleId":16,"question":"What three letters turn a girl into a woman?","answer":"Age","confusion_1":"Experience","confusion_2":"Love\r"},{"puzzleId":17,"question":"What has two legs but can not walk?","answer":"Compass","confusion_1":"The disabled","confusion_2":"Chair\r"},{"puzzleId":18,"question":"What animal is taller sitting down than standing up?","answer":"A dog","confusion_1":"A horse ","confusion_2":"A bird\r"},{"puzzleId":19,"question":"What can you catch but cannot see?","answer":"A cold","confusion_1":"A train","confusion_2":"A fish\r"},{"puzzleId":20,"question":"What is black when it's clean and white when it's dirty?","answer":"Blackboard","confusion_1":"The wall","confusion_2":"A painting\r"},{"puzzleId":21,"question":"What is deaf and dumb but always tells the truth?","answer":"A mirror","confusion_1":"A book","confusion_2":"A wise man\r"},{"puzzleId":22,"question":"What has teeth but cannot eat?","answer":"Comb","confusion_1":"Men with toothache","confusion_2":"Dead animals\r"},{"puzzleId":23,"question":"What question can you never answer yes to ?","answer":"Are you asleep?","confusion_1":"Are you single?","confusion_2":"DId you lie?\r"},{"puzzleId":24,"question":"Who always goes to bed with his shoes on?","answer":"A horse","confusion_1":"Someone loves to","confusion_2":"Nobody did this\r"},{"puzzleId":25,"question":"What has no leg but a body and a long neck?","answer":"A bottle","confusion_1":"An alien","confusion_2":"People with disease\r"},{"puzzleId":26,"question":"What is the best thing to keep in hot weather?","answer":"Keep cool","confusion_1":"Keep calm","confusion_2":"Keep money\r"},{"puzzleId":27,"question":"What can be measured but has no length, width or thickness?","answer":"The temperature","confusion_1":"It doesn't exist","confusion_2":"Your anger\r"},{"puzzleId":28,"question":"What person tried to make you smile most of the time?","answer":"A photographer","confusion_1":"A kind man","confusion_2":"My parents\r"},{"puzzleId":29,"question":"How many sides does a house have?","answer":"Two","confusion_1":"At least six","confusion_2":"Five sides\r"},{"puzzleId":30,"question":"What room has no walls, no doors, no windows, and no floors?","answer":"Mushroom","confusion_1":"That's ridiculous","confusion_2":"A prisoner cell\r"},{"puzzleId":31,"question":"The greater it is, the less it can be seen. What is it?","answer":"Darkness","confusion_1":"The hope","confusion_2":"Wealth\r"},{"puzzleId":32,"question":"What is dark but made by light?","answer":"A shadow","confusion_1":"The stars","confusion_2":"The moon\r"},{"puzzleId":33,"question":"What large instrument(乐器) do you carry in your ears?","answer":"Drum","confusion_1":"That's ridiculous","confusion_2":"Piano\r"},{"puzzleId":34,"question":"What is easy to get into but hard to get out of? ","answer":"Trouble","confusion_1":"A small hole","confusion_2":"A bus\r"},{"puzzleId":35,"question":"What two words have the most letters in it?","answer":"Post office","confusion_1":"Many letters","confusion_2":"A dictionary\r"},{"puzzleId":36,"question":"What animal wear big black glasses on its face?","answer":"Panda","confusion_1":"A cartoon cat","confusion_2":"A pet with glasses\r"},{"puzzleId":37,"question":"Why does the boy carry a ladder to the school?","answer":"He goes to high school","confusion_1":"He needs a ladder","confusion_2":"The way to school is hard\r"},{"puzzleId":38,"question":"What always travels on foot?","answer":"Shoes","confusion_1":"Animals","confusion_2":"Someone special\r"},{"puzzleId":39,"question":"Where can happiness always be found?","answer":"In the dictionary","confusion_1":"In our life","confusion_2":"During the love\r"},{"puzzleId":40,"question":"Why don't you advertise for your lost dog?","answer":"Dog can't read","confusion_1":"No money","confusion_2":"It's useless\r"},{"puzzleId":41,"question":"What is never used until its broken?","answer":"An egg","confusion_1":"An oath","confusion_2":"A bomb\r"},{"puzzleId":42,"question":"Where can milk be best stored?","answer":"In a cow","confusion_1":"In supermarket","confusion_2":"In refrigerator\r"},{"puzzleId":43,"question":"Whats the hardest thing about learning skating?","answer":"The ice","confusion_1":"Keep balance","confusion_2":"How to stop\r"},{"puzzleId":44,"question":"Why is it useless to send a letter to Washington?","answer":"He was dead","confusion_1":"It's too far ","confusion_2":"The address is miss\r"},{"puzzleId":45,"question":"What person does every man take his hat off to?","answer":"A barber","confusion_1":"Your boss","confusion_2":"Someone you respect\r"},{"puzzleId":46,"question":"What starts with a T, ends with a T, and is full of T?","answer":"Teapot","confusion_1":"T-shirt","confusion_2":"Tecent\r"},{"puzzleId":47,"question":"What could you see with your eyes shut?","answer":"A dream","confusion_1":"Nothing","confusion_2":"The darkness\r"},{"puzzleId":48,"question":"Which is the longest word in English?","answer":"Smiles","confusion_1":"Longest","confusion_2":"Manufacturing\r"},{"puzzleId":49,"question":"What can only run but can't walk?","answer":"Water","confusion_1":"A soccer player","confusion_2":"A marathon player\r"},{"puzzleId":50,"question":"What country is popular on Thanksgiving Day?","answer":"Turkey","confusion_1":"America","confusion_2":"China\r"},{"puzzleId":51,"question":"What nation is hated by schoolboys?","answer":"Examination","confusion_1":"China","confusion_2":"Japan\r"},{"puzzleId":52,"question":"If you throw a butter from a high place, what will you get?","answer":"A butterfly","confusion_1":"A butter still ","confusion_2":"Nothing left\r"},{"puzzleId":53,"question":"What animal is in every baseball game?","answer":"Bat","confusion_1":"Birds","confusion_2":"Insects\r"},{"puzzleId":54,"question":"What's yours but is used by others more than by yourself?","answer":"Your name","confusion_1":"Your money","confusion_2":"Your photo\r"},{"puzzleId":55,"question":"Where dose afternoon come before morning in the world?","answer":"In the dictionary","confusion_1":"In Europe","confusion_2":"In Arctic\r"},{"puzzleId":56,"question":"Why do birds fly south?","answer":"It's too far to walk","confusion_1":"South is warmer","confusion_2":"They are in north\r"},{"puzzleId":57,"question":"Who works only one day in a year but never gets fired?","answer":"Santa Claus","confusion_1":"The boss","confusion_2":"Some rich people\r"},{"puzzleId":58,"question":"What, by losing one eye, has nothing left but a nose？","answer":"Noise","confusion_1":"SIngle eye monster","confusion_2":"Elephant\r"},{"puzzleId":59,"question":"Why do lions eat raw meat?","answer":"They can't cook","confusion_1":"They are animals","confusion_2":"They love it\r"},{"puzzleId":60,"question":"What does everybody do at the same time?","answer":"Grow old","confusion_1":"Watch World Cup","confusion_2":"Play LOL\r"},{"puzzleId":61,"question":"What is it that everyone wants to have and get rid of too?","answer":"Appetite","confusion_1":"Age","confusion_2":"Duty\r"},{"puzzleId":62,"question":"How do we know the ocean is so friendly?","answer":"It waves","confusion_1":"It's calm","confusion_2":"The water is gentle\r"},{"puzzleId":63,"question":"What clothing is always sad?   ","answer":"Blue jeans","confusion_1":"Clothing with holes","confusion_2":"Weary cloths\r"},{"puzzleId":64,"question":"What is the smallest bridge in the world?","answer":"The bridge of a nose","confusion_1":"A model bridge","confusion_2":"Cambridge\r"},{"puzzleId":65,"question":"Which month do soldiers hate?","answer":"March","confusion_1":"All the months","confusion_2":"October\r"},{"puzzleId":66,"question":"What driver doesn't have a license?","answer":"Screwdriver","confusion_1":"A terrible driver","confusion_2":"A drunk driver\r"},{"puzzleId":67,"question":"What makes opening piano so hard?","answer":"Keys are inside","confusion_1":"The lid is too heavy","confusion_2":"Something is wrong\r"},{"puzzleId":68,"question":"What's the heaviest thing in the world?","answer":"Eyelids","confusion_1":"Duty","confusion_2":"Gold\r"},{"puzzleId":69,"question":"What is it that is always coming but never arrives?","answer":"Tomorrow","confusion_1":"A beautiful wife","confusion_2":"A handsome husband\r"},{"puzzleId":70,"question":"When does a doctor get angry？","answer":"Lose his patient","confusion_1":"Too many patients","confusion_2":"He worked too long\r"},{"puzzleId":71,"question":"What's the difference between a woman and an unbrella?","answer":"Umbrella could shut up","confusion_1":"They're different things","confusion_2":"Umbrella isn't alive\r"},{"puzzleId":72,"question":"What do you still keep after giving it to someone else?","answer":"Your word","confusion_1":"Your memory","confusion_2":"Your money\r"},{"puzzleId":73,"question":"What is it that falls often but never gets hurt?","answer":"Snow","confusion_1":"Hail","confusion_2":"Branches\r"},{"puzzleId":74,"question":"What's too much for one, but nothing at all for many people?","answer":"A secret","confusion_1":"A promise","confusion_2":"A lie\r"},{"puzzleId":75,"question":"What do you call a man with a car on his head？","answer":"Jack","confusion_1":"Rose","confusion_2":"Tom\r"},{"puzzleId":76,"question":"Who is closer to you, your mom or dad?","answer":"Mom, father is farther","confusion_1":"The same","confusion_2":"My dad\r"},{"puzzleId":77,"question":"What is it that everybody gives but few take?","answer":"Advice","confusion_1":"Praise","confusion_2":"Criticism\r"},{"puzzleId":78,"question":"A farmer has 17 sheep and nine die. How many are left?","answer":"Nine","confusion_1":"Eight left","confusion_2":"No sheep left\r"},{"puzzleId":79,"question":"Which seven-letter word contains dozens of letters?","answer":"Mailbox","confusion_1":"Letters","confusion_2":"Massive\r"},{"puzzleId":80,"question":"Which is heavier? A pound of feathers or a pound of rocks?","answer":"Both weigh a pound","confusion_1":"Feather is heavier","confusion_2":"Rock is heavier\r"},{"puzzleId":81,"question":"What word becomes shorter when you add two letters to it?","answer":"Short","confusion_1":"Are you kidding","confusion_2":"Smaller\r"},{"puzzleId":82,"question":"What can be seen once in a minute and never in future?","answer":"The letter M","confusion_1":"A shooting star","confusion_2":"A opportunity\r"},{"puzzleId":83,"question":"Which tire doesn't move when a car turns right?","answer":"The spire tire","confusion_1":"That's impossible","confusion_2":"It depends on direction\r"},{"puzzleId":84,"question":"Which word is written incorrectly in a dictionary?","answer":"The word incorrectly","confusion_1":"Mistake is avoidable","confusion_2":"No such word\r"},{"puzzleId":85,"question":"What travels around the world staying in the same corner?","answer":"A stamp","confusion_1":"Nothing could do this","confusion_2":"A plane\r"},{"puzzleId":86,"question":"Which hand is best for stirring sugar into a cup of coffee?","answer":"A spoon is better","confusion_1":"Left hand","confusion_2":"Right hand\r"},{"puzzleId":87,"question":"What has 5 fingers but is not alive?","answer":"A glove","confusion_1":"A starfish","confusion_2":"A hand\r"},{"puzzleId":88,"question":"What word begins and ends with an E but only has one letter?","answer":"Envelope","confusion_1":"Eye","confusion_2":"The letter E\r"},{"puzzleId":89,"question":"How many months have 28 days?","answer":"All 12 months","confusion_1":"Only February","confusion_2":"One month\r"},{"puzzleId":90,"question":"What has one eye but can't see?","answer":"A needle","confusion_1":"Men with eye diseases","confusion_2":"A blind man\r"},{"puzzleId":91,"question":"What keys can't open any door?","answer":"Monkey","confusion_1":"A broken key ","confusion_2":"The wrong key\r"},{"puzzleId":92,"question":"What invention lets you look right through a wall?","answer":"A window","confusion_1":"A special device","confusion_2":"A telescope\r"},{"puzzleId":93,"question":"What kind of coat can only be put on when wet?","answer":"A coat of paint","confusion_1":"A rain coat","confusion_2":"Any coats could\r"},{"puzzleId":94,"question":"What gets sharper the more you use it?","answer":"Your brain","confusion_1":"A pencil","confusion_2":"A knife\r"},{"puzzleId":95,"question":"What is full of holes but can still hold water?","answer":"A sponge","confusion_1":"A well","confusion_2":"A bucket with holes\r"},{"puzzleId":96,"question":"What ends in everything always?","answer":"The letter G","confusion_1":"A good ending","confusion_2":"A bad ending\r"},{"puzzleId":97,"question":"What are brothers from the same mother but never meet?","answer":"Day and night","confusion_1":"The lost brothers","confusion_2":"The shoes\r"},{"puzzleId":98,"question":"What use ears to speak and mouthes to hear?","answer":"A phone","confusion_1":"Abnormal creature","confusion_2":"It doesn't exist\r"},{"puzzleId":99,"question":"What can only carry lots of food but cannot eat anything?","answer":"A refrigerator","confusion_1":"A waiter","confusion_2":"A plate\r"},{"puzzleId":100,"question":"What you can only eat at night but never in morning?","answer":"Dinner","confusion_1":"A big meal","confusion_2":"Steak\r"},{"puzzleId":101,"question":"What you cannot come in or go out without it?","answer":"A door","confusion_1":"Your shoes","confusion_2":"A very big thing\r"},{"puzzleId":102,"question":"What is excellent to taste but cannot smell?","answer":"A tongue","confusion_1":"Some food","confusion_2":"It doesn't exist\r"},{"puzzleId":103,"question":"What has lots of money but can never spend any money?","answer":"A purse","confusion_1":"An economist","confusion_2":"A thrifty man\r"},{"puzzleId":104,"question":"What is made of water but is not wet?","answer":"A woman","confusion_1":"Watermelon","confusion_2":"A cloud"}]}